[
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This 1970's era Republican hard rock guitarist once referred to former President Barack Obama as a \"subhuman mongrel.\" ",
        "correct": "Ted Nugent",
        "answerA": "Ted Nugent",
        "answerB": "Peter Frampton",
        "answerC": "Jeff Beck",
        "answerD": "Eric Clapton"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- The Geto Boys released this women hating, anti- abortion song in 1993.",
        "correct": "\"The Unseen\"",
        "answerA": "\"The Unseen\"",
        "answerB": "\"The Unheard\"",
        "answerC": "\"The Last Fetus\"",
        "answerD": "\"The Lost Fetus\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In what 1975 song did Ted Nugent sing about strangling a women who tried to leave him?",
        "correct": "\"Stranglehold\"",
        "answerA": "\"Stranglehold\"",
        "answerB": "\"Free for All\"",
        "answerC": "\"Wango Tango\"",
        "answerD": "\"Cat Scratch Fever\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Which \"objectivist\" philosopher and libertarian icon is mentioned in the liner notes of Rush's 1976 album 2112? ",
        "correct": "Ayn Rand",
        "answerA": "Ayn Rand",
        "answerB": "Alan Greenspan",
        "answerC": "Murray Rothbard",
        "answerD": "John Hospers"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- What Guns and Roses song off their 1989 album G N R Lies decries \"niggers, immigrants, faggots and police?\"",
        "correct": "\"One in a Million\"",
        "answerA": "\"One in a Million\"",
        "answerB": "\"Radicals and Racists\"",
        "answerC": "\"Way too High\"",
        "answerD": "\"Small Town White Boy\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This lead singer for the legendary Southern, California punk band X, described herself as a conspiracy theorist and Trump supporter in 2017.",
        "correct": "Exene Cervenka",
        "answerA": "Exene Cervenka",
        "answerB": "Linda Perry",
        "answerC": "Alice Bag",
        "answerD": "Johnette Napolitano"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Morrissey, the former lead singer of the Smiths, labeled this ethno-nationality \"sub-human\" due to \"their\" treatment of animals.",
        "correct": "The Chinese",
        "answerA": "The Chinese",
        "answerB": "The Brazilians",
        "answerC": "The Americans",
        "answerD": "The Turks"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- The German, heavy metal band, the Scorpions, released an album in 1976 with a naked, prepubescent girl in a sexual pose on the cover. What was the name of the record?",
        "correct": "Virgin Killers",
        "answerA": "Virgin Killers",
        "answerB": "Animal Magnetism",
        "answerC": "Virgin Hunters",
        "answerD": "Love Drive"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In what year was Ozzy Osbourne arrested for domestic violence?",
        "correct": "1989",
        "answerA": "1989",
        "answerB": "1993",
        "answerC": "1975",
        "answerD": "2001"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- At a 1976 concert in the U.K. Eric Clapton said \"Stop Britain from becoming a black colony...Keep Britain white!\" These comments led to the creation of what organization? ",
        "correct": "Rock Against Racism",
        "answerA": "Rock Against Racism",
        "answerB": "Rock Against the Right",
        "answerC": "Rock Against Hate",
        "answerD": "Rock for Peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- R.J. Smith's 2012 biography, The One, detailed which funk music legend's history of domestic violence against women?",
        "correct": "James Brown",
        "answerA": "James Brown",
        "answerB": "Leroy Bonner",
        "answerC": "Bootsy Collins",
        "answerD": "George Clinton"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Sid Vicious was regularly known to walk around London wearing this symbol of hate.",
        "correct": "The Nazi Swastika",
        "answerA": "The Nazi Swastika",
        "answerB": "The Confederate Stars and Bars",
        "answerC": "Saint George's Cross",
        "answerD": "The Union Jack"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Which Ramone was a right-wing Republican and a supporter of George W Bush during his 2004 campaign?",
        "correct": "Johnny Ramone",
        "answerA": "Johnny Ramone",
        "answerB": "Dee Dee Ramone",
        "answerC": "Marky Ramone",
        "answerD": "Joey Ramone"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This Christian emo-rock group released an anti-affirmative action song in 1998 called \"One.\" ",
        "correct": "Creed",
        "answerA": "Creed",
        "answerB": "Candlebox",
        "answerC": "Three Doors Down",
        "answerD": "Coldplay"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In 1999 Gary Glitter was convicted and sentenced in the UK for what?",
        "correct": "Downloading child porn",
        "answerA": "Downloading child porn",
        "answerB": "Have sex with a minor",
        "answerC": "Public indecency",
        "answerD": "Child abuse"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This glam rock icon, known for assuming different personas over his career, made a number of pro-fascist statements as \"The Thin White Duke\" in the mid 1970's.",
        "correct": "David Bowie",
        "answerA": "David Bowie",
        "answerB": "Peter Murphy",
        "answerC": "Johnny Thunders",
        "answerD": "T-Rex"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Which right-wing talk radio host has used the Pretender's \"My City Was Gone\" as the intro to his daily show since 1988? ",
        "correct": "Rush Limbaugh",
        "answerA": "Rush Limbaugh",
        "answerB": "David Brudnoy",
        "answerC": "Bob Grant",
        "answerD": "Sean Hannity"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- On what album did the misogynous song \"I Use to Love Her but I had to Kill Her\" from the heavy metal group Guns and Roses appear? ",
        "correct": "G N' R Lies",
        "answerA": "G N' R Lies",
        "answerB": "Chinese Democracy",
        "answerC": "Appetite for Destruction",
        "answerD": "Use Your Illusion II"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This song by the group Lynyrd Skynyrd was an answer to the Crosby, Stills, Nash and Neil Young anti-racist songs \"Southern Man\" and \"Alabama.\"",
        "correct": "\"Sweet Home Alabama\"",
        "answerA": "\"Sweet Home Alabama\"",
        "answerB": "\"Gimme Back My Bullets\"",
        "answerC": "\"Freebird\"",
        "answerD": "\"Saturday Night Special\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Who did hip- hop artist LL Cool J support for president in 2004?",
        "correct": "John McCain",
        "answerA": "John McCain",
        "answerB": "George W Bush",
        "answerC": "Howard Dean",
        "answerD": "Mike Huckabee"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- How many times has Tommy Lee, former lead guitarist for Motley Crew, been arrested for domestic violence?",
        "correct": "Twice-1994 and 1998",
        "answerA": "Twice-1994 and 1999",
        "answerB": "Four times- 1986, 1999, 2003, 2009",
        "answerC": "Once- 1997",
        "answerD": "Three times- 2002, 2007 and 2008"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Who wrote and performed the song  \"Some Niggers Never Die (They Just Smell That Way)\" ",
        "correct": "Johnny Rebel",
        "answerA": "Johnny Rebel",
        "answerB": "The Rebel Dixie Band",
        "answerC": "Dixie Johnny",
        "answerD": "Johnny Dixie"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Which late 1970's and 80's dark wave band did the song \"Killing an Arab\" based on the book The Stranger by Albert Camus? ",
        "correct": "The Cure",
        "answerA": "The Cure",
        "answerB": "The Smiths",
        "answerC": "Simple Minds",
        "answerD": "The Jam"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Rapper Ice-T, lead singer for the band Body Count (famous for the 1990 song \"Cop Killer\"), went on to play a cop in what long running cable T.V. show?",
        "correct": "Law and Order- SVU",
        "answerA": "Law and Order- SVU",
        "answerB": "Law and Order- Criminal Intent",
        "answerC": "New Jack City- the Series",
        "answerD": "Colors- the Series"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Green Day left this Berkeley, California Indy label that helped launch their career in 2005 over years of unpaid royalties.",
        "correct": "Lookout Records",
        "answerA": "Lookout Records",
        "answerB": "Matador Records",
        "answerC": "Discord Records",
        "answerD": "Epitaph Records"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In their 1978 song \"Some Girls\" the Rolling Stones claimed that black girls just want to what? ",
        "correct": "\"get fucked all night\"",
        "answerA": "\"get fucked all night\"",
        "answerB": "\"holla and fight all night\"",
        "answerC": "\"do blow all night\"",
        "answerD": "\"party all night\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- On what 1992 song does Ice Cube demand that Koreans in LA \"pay respect to the black fist or we'll burn your store right down to a crisp?\" ",
        "correct": "\"Black Korea\"",
        "answerA": "\"Black Korea\"",
        "answerB": "\"Black Vietnam\"",
        "answerC": "\"Black Japan\"",
        "answerD": "\"Black Chinatown\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Elvis Presley was once quoted as saying \"the only thing black people can do for me is shine my shoes and...\"  ",
        "correct": "\"buy my records\"",
        "answerA": "\"buy my records\"",
        "answerB": "\"sing the blues\"",
        "answerC": "\"piss off\"",
        "answerD": "\"kiss my ass\""
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In a now infamous 2003 video for the song \"Tip Drill,\" this hip- hop artist runs a credit card between the buttocks of black female dancers.",
        "correct": "Nelly",
        "answerA": "Nelly",
        "answerB": "Usher",
        "answerC": "Ludacris",
        "answerD": "R Kelly"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Which famous rap artist came out in support of Donald Trump in 2018?",
        "correct": "Kayne West",
        "answerA": "Kayne West",
        "answerB": "Kendrick Lamar",
        "answerC": "Jay-Z",
        "answerD": "P. Diddy"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This female, dark wave pioneer was photographed wearing swastika t-shirts in a number of pictures in the late 1970's.",
        "correct": "Siouxsie of Siouxsie and the Banshees",
        "answerA": "Siouxsie of Siouxsie and the Banshees",
        "answerB": "Exene Cervenka of X",
        "answerC": "Kim Gordon of South Youth",
        "answerD": "Wendy O' Williams of the Plasmatics"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This American pop singer, was arrested in 2009 for domestic violence against the pop music singer Rihanna.",
        "correct": "Chris Brown",
        "answerA": "Chris Brown",
        "answerB": "Lil Wayne",
        "answerC": "Drake",
        "answerD": "Usher"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In 2018 this pop singer, and President Trump supporter, turned up to the Grammys in a white dress with a painted fetus on it and a purse that said \"Choose Life.\"",
        "correct": "Joy Villa",
        "answerA": "Joy Villa",
        "answerB": "Joan Armatrading",
        "answerC": "Tracy Chapman",
        "answerD": "Alicia Keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- Elvis Costello once referred to which African American blues icon as an \"ignorant nigger?\" ",
        "correct": "Ray Charles",
        "answerA": "Ray Charles",
        "answerB": "Bo Diddley",
        "answerC": "Albert King",
        "answerD": "BB King"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- This multi-platinum hip- hop artist claimed in a May 2018 interview with TMZ that \"slavery was a choice.\" ",
        "correct": "Kayne West",
        "answerA": "Kayne West",
        "answerB": "Wiz Khalifa",
        "answerC": "50 Cent",
        "answerD": "Lil Wayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these U.S. based rappers did not support President Trump in the 2020 election?",
        "correct": "Chuck D",
        "answerA": "Chuck D",
        "answerB": "Ice Cube",
        "answerC": "50 Cent",
        "answerD": "Lil Wayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "HALL OF LAME- In the 1983 Beastie Boys song \"Girls,\" they're good to have around to do what?",
        "correct": "\"Do the dishes, clean up my room, do the laundry…\"",
        "answerA": "\"Do the dishes, clean up my room, do the laundry…\"",
        "answerB": "\"To scratch my itch and kiss my grits...\"",
        "answerC": "\"Scrub the floor and be my whore...\"",
        "answerD": "\"Scrub and clean my house, then bounce...\""
    }
]